{"type":"multiple","question":"Which actress has featured in films including Moulin Rouge! and Aquaman?","correct_answer":"Nicole Kidman","incorrect_answers":["Natalie Portman", "Kate Winslet", "Maggie Smith"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'Three policemen investigate a series of murders with their own brand of justice.'","correct_answer":"L.A. Confidential","incorrect_answers":["Aliens", "Schindler's List", "Raging Bull"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Who was Cary Grant's female lead in the movie 'To catch a thief?","correct_answer":"Grace Kelly","incorrect_answers":["Marylin Monroe", "Hedy Lamarr", "Rita Hayworth"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Addis Ababa is a city in which country?","correct_answer":"Ethiopia","incorrect_answers":["Tunisia", "South Africa", "Democratic Republic of the Congo"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 1986?","correct_answer":"Platoon","incorrect_answers":["Children of a Lesser God", "Hannah and Her Sisters", "The Mission"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Macaulay Caulkin's folks left him \","correct_answer":"Paris","incorrect_answers":["New York", "London", "Sydney"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which word is defined as 'having wooly or crispy hair'?","correct_answer":"Ulotrichous","incorrect_answers":["Conjubilant", "Kakorrhaphiophobia", "Sprunt"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"What is the chemical deuterium oxide often used for?","correct_answer":"It is used in nuclear reactors, as a neutron moderator.","incorrect_answers":["It is commonly used as a condiment and food preservative.", "It is used for surface purification, bleaching, odour removal and water disinfection.", "It us used in baking to stabilize egg whites."]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which region of the world uses '.pf' at the end of its web addresses?","correct_answer":"Tahiti","incorrect_answers":["The Philippines", "South Africa", "Palau"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which word refers to the ceremony in which a new President of the United States is formally introduced?","correct_answer":"Inauguration","incorrect_answers":["Coronation", "Installation", "Ordination"]}"comment":"""stats":""